<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2018 Luya Tshimbalanga <luya_tfz@thefinalzone.net> -->
<component type="desktop-application">
​  <id>com.elsevier.MendeleyDesktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPLv2+ and Mendeley and MIT and CC-BY-SA and (CPAL or AGPLv3) and BSD</project_license>
  <name>Mendeley Desktop</name>
  <summary>Academic reference management software for researchers</summary>

  <description>
    <p>
      Mendeley is a combination of a desktop application and a website which
      helps you manage, share and discover both content and contacts in research.
    </p>
    <p>Our software, Mendeley Desktop, offers you:</p>
    <ul>
       <li>
         Automatic extraction of document details (authors, title, journal etc.)
         from academic papers into a library database, which saves you a lot of
         manual typing! As more people use Mendeley, the quality of the data
         extraction improves.
       </li>
       <li>
         Super-efficient management of your papers: "Live" full-text search across
         all your papers – the results start to appear as you type! Mendeley
         Desktop also lets you filter your library by authors, journals or keywords.
         You can also use document collections, notes and tags to organize your
         knowledge, and export the document details in different citation styles.
       </li>
       <li>
         Sharing and synchronization of your library (or parts of it) with
         selected colleagues. This is perfect for jointly managing all the papers in
         your lab!
       </li>
       <li>
         More great features: A plug-in for citing your articles in Microsoft
         Word, OCR (image-to-text conversion, so you can full-text search all your
         scanned PDFs) and lots more new features being worked upon.
       </li>
​    </ul>
​  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">mendeleydesktop.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Mendeley Desktop in default Library as Table view</caption>
      <image>https://raw.github.com/hmaarrfk/mendeley-rpm/master/images/mendeley-desktop_2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Login session</caption>
      <image>https://raw.github.com/hmaarrfk/mendeley-rpm/master/images/mendeley-desktop_0.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Welcome dialog</caption>
      <image>https://raw.github.com/hmaarrfk/mendeley-rpm/master/images/mendeley-desktop_1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Mendeley Desktop in Library as Citation view</caption>
      <image>https://raw.github.com/hmaarrfk/mendeley-rpm/master/images/mendeley-desktop_3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://www.mendeley.com</url>
  <project_group>Mendeley</project_group>

  <provides>
    <binary>mendeleydesktop</binary>
  </provides>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.19.3" date="2019-01-01">
      <description>
	<p>We have fixed the following bugs:</p>
	<ul>
​	  <li>In the library:
             <ul>
              <li>The ‘Read’ column has been restored in the Recently Read view</li>
              <li>The application is no longer unresponsive during automatic backups</li>
              <li>Annotations can now be moved after they have been created</li>
              <li>Annotations are no longer displaying as ‘Unknown user’ for all exported annotations</li>
             </ul>
          </li>
          <li>In the LibreOffice citation plugin:
	     <ul>
              <li>Adjacent inline or footnote citations no longer fail to merge when cited in a table</li>
              <li>Sync to fail when the user profile was not synced</li>
             </ul>
	  </li>
	</ul>
​      </description>
​    </release>
​  </releases>
</component>
