<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2018 Luya Tshimbalanga <luya_tfz@thefinalzone.net> -->
<component type="desktop-application">
​  <id>com.mendeley.mendeleydesktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPLv2+ and Mendeley and MIT and CC-BY-SA and (CPAL or AGPLv3) and BSD</project_license>
  <name>Power Statistics</name>
  <summary>Observe power management</summary>

  <description>
    <p>
      Mendeley is a combination of a desktop application and a website which
      helps you manage, share and discover both content and contacts in research.
    </p>
    <p>Our software, Mendeley Desktop, offers you:</p>
    <ul>
       <li>
         Automatic extraction of document details (authors, title, journal etc.)
         from academic papers into a library database, which saves you a lot of
         manual typing! As more people use Mendeley, the quality of the data
         extraction improves.
       </li>
       <li>
         Super-efficient management of your papers: "Live" full-text search across
         all your papers – the results start to appear as you type! Mendeley
         Desktop also lets you filter your library by authors, journals or keywords.
         You can also use document collections, notes and tags to organize your
         knowledge, and export the document details in different citation styles.
       </li>
       <li>
         Sharing and synchronization of your library (or parts of it) with
         selected colleagues. This is perfect for jointly managing all the papers in
         your lab!
       </li>
       <li>
         More great features: A plug-in for citing your articles in Microsoft
         Word, OCR (image-to-text conversion, so you can full-text search all your
         scanned PDFs) and lots more new features being worked upon.
       </li>
​    </ul>
​  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">mendeleydesktop.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
​    <screenshot type="default">
​      <caption>The user interface</caption>
      <image>https://2.bp.blogspot.com/-oZnl3C750Qg/TxmKMJgfdhI/AAAAAAAAHdM/LNwTZC-UE8o/s1600/mendeley-desktop_3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://www.mendeley.com</url>
  <project_group>Mendeley</project_group>

  <provides>
    <binary>mendeleydesktop</binary>
  </provides>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.19.2" date="2018-01-01">
      <description>
	<ul>
​	  <li>The database back-up feature has been restored.</li>
          <li>We fixed bugs that were causing the app to crash during:
             <ul>
              <li>Sync</li>
              <li>PDF import; and</li>
              <li>Opening a corrupted database</li>
             </ul>
          </li>
          <li>We also fixed two bugs relating to sync causing:
	     <ul>
              <li>Incorrect sync for users using the app on more than one machine</li>
              <li>Sync to fail when the user profile was not synced</li>
             </ul>
	  </li>
	</ul>
​      </description>
​    </release>
​  </releases>
</component>
